all right everyone let's do this first
of all for the first movie deck BAM
you're gonna want to run fear these bad
boys
Sonic the Hedgehog himself Sonic is the
main search of this deck oh my
God and he does it so well when song is
summoned to the field normal summon you
can get a Hedgehog any Hedgehog
from your deck and put it in your
head
there's three of them in this deck Sonic
nansuk magna honking Sonia the Hedgehog
we uses it effect most of the time
you're going to want to summon one of
his saves and that's it if you're gonna
want to get most time is Sonia what
Sonia does is when she is in your hand
and you got heads I'm gonna feel it lock
stock you can special summon that
you do that so has all the effect
activates and then you can get another
Hedgehog BAM Manic the badass himself
from your deck into your hand as you can
see Simon sir they all have a ways to
get themselves from the deck to the hand
with each other there is why few knows I
only run - Sonja's into Max because
Sonic is the main search of the back
he's the one you were gonna want to run
at 3 the other two they're just they
love that do to make sock look good
so yeah oh my God next mmm oh my God
Bobby you're gonna want to run three bar
base because he's so good when
he special summoned you get 1,000 Life
Points oh my God that's so good
you're Paul Wong till 5 that's
overpowered no one ain't no one ain't do
I slap your ass you'll see why it's so
good so as I was saying when box was on
you gets 1,000 points
now you buy one these four styles how
you gonna special summon in that's for
later I'll show you why boom
Dame's got big ass mmm next now you
bought one drink
these are these heads are pretty
download well you know and their money
Roger that in a kid Nanjing not cuz the
Echidna you know where this BAM
three Knuckles one of those badasses
three of those badasses
what Knuckles does see garlic of a very
he's got a unique playstyle he he's
really just he's a known monster however
he's got many support cards that make
him pretty bitching if you ask
me so yeah you'll see why I mean by
running an Echidna engine in the sack
after that you're gonna want to dam is a
big boobies you're gonna want to run
like two minutes she really don't do
all is if she's a last caught in
your hand you can special summon and you
get to draw two cards
the thing is the Hedgehogs they always
search each other you're always gonna
have you always just multiple times so
you're never gonna be without card in
your hand
although I'm just gonna throw out I was
here throwing up at Scott big boobies so
yeah
last but not least foot to finish off
the monsters don't they want to want to
run the final Uncle Chuck now you're
probably wondering did I why do only one
run one Uncle Chuck what it's because he
he's name is Uncle Chuck he does not
count as a Hedgehog so he cannot be
searched by Sonic Manic or Sonya so
really that's all he is he's just a
sixth I'll be a twenty four attack
2,300 defense and his affects us when
this card is sent from the hand or deck
grab you can spare some in defense mode
although his defense cannot be cannot be
changed Pacey yeah I put in there for
Vlad he's also a tuna too so yeah that
mean these are tuna as well so yeah I
guess you can see I got some signals
coming up who's right see some spells
and trash
I know I am alright bitches first of all
full of smells
you're going to want to run triple
lovers kiss what the days pictures
so cute
I drew that oh my God what lovers kiss
us you may have your lifeboats to some a
song and Bobby from your deck and put it
onto the field
oh my God that is good holy
after that you're going to want to run
you're gonna want to run two of these
pieces of ass mean dick yeah I love men
dick
what men dig dust you can fetch my Mac
straight from the deck onto the field
oh my God then you eat it's our dog you
thought that was it nor a damn what
disgust when you do that spur son back
from the deck onto the field you can
clip this humanik he cannot be affecting
us perhaps oh wait yeah he cannot be
affected by all that's holy that's
good also when the season and get maybe
from your deck put it in your
hand as if it wasn't cool enough
after that you can want to want to other
field spells over stick memories witness
cars activate you can tackle one car he
puts out the field we tell that of
an awesome every time your opponent
summons a crowd you just draw
out like once per ton that's
good I drew that toe damn I drew this
one too what do all this the hope
in our hands come on you want to run two
of these damn sorry Max crying can
sign up great nice boobies uh damn hmm
what this car does this get any number
of Munson you great up pay 1000 each and
summon em cuz I feel and they cannot you
cannot connect in to give a face of the
team do but still gets the job done sets
up for four plays they're on you know
after that you're going to work we're on
a time of peace gets rid of one car on
the special shop on your pulse on the
field gets rid of that back rolling
I know it's gay with the back row BAM a
dangerous mission he's got one kind of
ham destroyed to spell it out cuz I pass
our field Dan that's good now oh my God
mm this one's good hmm one man's Val
this damn that one that's too sexy
okay coach on the game oh my God what
this guy does is rip locks
closing oh my God that's good this
with all monsters on your points out of
the field
oh come on three this yeah I don't
that's good last but not least you're
going to run the longest limo in the
world
damn discount one month I'll just have
to fit and you then you can sum and up
to two Bobby's from your deck so that's
1000 e g+ 2005 points and two monsters
awful discount one month audience I feel
that's broken you know what Hank no name
it's fair alright I won't move our
traps first of all as I got the Knuckles
engine here we go talk to beginning
oxygen you going want to run three of
the last Echidna what this car does and
let you get any KKnux a spell
trap from your deck and put it set a
face alright I just have a field and
every single time you're gonna play this
card you want to get learn to overcome
this is ugly in my opinion the best
couch in my deck mainly for its
versatility
besides the love of hiss where this car
does is as long as face up on the field
once per turn doing every one of your
turns you can summon Knuckles from your
hacker graves out for free I'm not
kidding it's that good so yeah yeah with
this it really helps this deck with
consistency make you something things
like X Y Z's synch with all that good
after that you want to run three
that's it from KKnux on you by the way
I think going for on three a heroes God
damn it's good when you pause it cuz
attack you can use this to get the
attack and just who all attack but some
ice on your points out of field next
you're gonna want to play to to the
horizons you all know what that uh
something about explain that
and then lastly you going to play two of
a father's sacrifice sacrifice this car
negate a negates what you're the one of
your pawn attack and ends the
bow face and then when the game Bassett
and Mindy from the deck to your hands so
yeah this something from India I guess
so now this will get you the bread and
butter down the the
extra deck
we'll all the good is as you say as
you'll remember I run a very strong
Hedgehog engine so for the first ones
you're going to want to run double Elena
the Hedgehog what's great about this one
is you do not Eve always is polarization
each the two edge of muscle on the field
simply gave up turn olena the Hedgehog
it's great because she actually counts
as a Hedgehog monster so she works very
well with the headaches perhaps the next
excerpt of our to Queen Elena's to make
this one you need to summon three you
need a fuse three Hedgehogs but it's
worth it maybe because she has a very
very powerful faxed when you're pulling
acting's effect or spill or checkup you
can discard SIM card from your hand at
the same time to get that next for
that you're going to want to run to
Knuckles the assassins this really helps
with the Knuckles out top in my deck in
the knuckle engine will it's more
he's really mean the toy farmed
betta
however you can disk you can detach more
material from this year to some looks
from the grave so yeah after that you're
going to want to run this is the best
in the whole deck
Bobby Montclair dressing he's a little
expose I hate takes is two little
monsters he's 2400 attack
damn and when Bobby is all filled
detached to material from him just tree
one kind balls are filled and when he
power this count is just is just super
battle or just between user move from
the field you can actually summon it
came as only a five card from your deck
ignoring the Sun conditions which all
the time you're gonna go into this one
this is these two these two right here I
was the best cousing retired compiler
doesn't and he's only five white and
darkness like they parallel each other
like yin and yang it's like poetic and
so oh my God oh my God
lastly you're gonna want to run for the
blast one is found boy Bobby and Found
boy Sonic he's a three thousand beater
but oh my God he just he takes for love
for summon but it's good because we're
both had some of them us you can detest
more from this to summon it
I no no not summon it to negate to
summon so yeah that's extra deck hope
you guys liked it I know I did